Contact

rowan2517@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angelacastillo2517 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Healthcare

Hospitals

Certifications

Registered Nurse

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

BLS

Registered Nurse

Angela Castillo

Registered Nurse at HonorHealth

Phoenix, Arizona Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Patient Education, Medicare, U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Nursing Science from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

HonorHealth
Registered Nurse
April 2020 - Present (4 months)
Phoenix, Arizona, United States

Swedish Medical Center

4 years 2 months

Charge Nurse October 2016 - April 2020 (3 years 7 months) Issaquah

Registered Nurse

March 2016 - October 2016 (8 months)

Issaquah

Banner Health

3 years 9 months

Registered Nurse

March 2015 - February 2016 (1 year)

Sun City, AZ

Patient safety and education, quality care

Patient Financial Services Representative June 2012 - March 2015 (2 years 10 months) Resolve patient concerns, collect patient responsibilities at time of service, verify insurance coverage

Cigna

Front office representative 2006 - 2010 (4 years)

Resolve patient concerns, collect patient responsibilities at time of service, confirmed appointments

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master's Degree, Nursing Education · (2015 - 2017)

Glendale Community College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing · (2012 - 2014)

Northern Arizona University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2014)